I did it last point for you, I would call the order of the minus special utility authority board meeting for December 13, 2021 and with two live invocation by Pastor First United Methodist Church, Miss Susan Rice.
Will this pick to you?
Yes.
Okay.
Great.
Gracious God.
We thank you for the opportunity to serve and to serve our community and we ask that you would bless this meeting that we have today.
May we hear each other as we listen to the business and as we move forward,
we bring a consensus as submission, one to another and exchange of ideas and opinions and we thank you,
God, for your presence in Jesus' name.
Amen.
I'd like to lead us to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God, and to it's will deliver to you and justice for our all.
For the Republic of Empower on Skate of Personal Parenthesis, five consent agenda staff recommends we approve, I am six and seven.
So, my.
Like.
Don't go.
Hi.
Davis.
All right.
Estep.
Stunberg.
Hi.
Parker.
Hey.
You did a strike in claim and David Stracht from Maine for the RDA Re licensing.
The mayor members of the Council of this is a claim for the two legal invoices that we receive.
These were discussed in our last executive session in pretty good detail.
As we knew that they were going to be fairly substantial.
Again, these were discussed in significant work had been done over the month of October, which is what is represented in these invoices,
which was things such as the review of the hydrologic and hydraulic study.
The review of the initial study report from GRDA.
The preparation of questions for the initial study report that occurred on October 12th and 13th.
The negotiation mayer that that you and I both were aware of and involved in regarding the meet and hunt operations manual.
Ultimately resulting in a furt protective order, which was in the city's favor and protects the city greatly and receiving that operations model.
And then also preparing written comments to the initial study report, which again is extremely important for the city.
As this is really our only opportunity to weigh in on the study that's being done for the re-licensing of Pensacola Dam, which ultimately gerda is requesting to raise the leg level by two feet in extend the license for 50 years.
Both of those things could have substantial impact on our community and citizens.
So it's important that we review that properly and provide all of our written comments.
2GRDA and 2 FERC.
It reverses that.
The happy answer to any questions anybody has.
Is this on page 16 of the packet?
Nothing at all.
Yes.
And so the total is 90,000 and 28 dollars.
Correct.
And this is not to, this is to help us with understanding the effects that this re-licensing would have on our area.
Yes.
That would be the bulk of the work done on this particular invoice was for the re-licensing.
Which is.
But down for us to understand how the impact of their re-licensing process is going to be, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Any other questions for both?
We'll make a motion that we approve.
Second.
He said.
I.
Davis.
Don't call.
I.
Semberg.
Dan.
Marker.
I.
Nine.
Except.
And a war bid for six and a nine-day infrastructure extension bid.
C21-56.
Put contract contingent upon approval.
Contracts documents.
And approve city manager.
Or is it doesn't need to sign.
Notice.
Proceed.
It's recommended.
Plus that.
Give me.
Maybe.
We open the bill.
Thursday.
For the sixty-nine days.
St. Shakespeare.
Project.
That three better.
Turn in.
We'll be at.
Is.
Circle B.
For.
is about 10,000 feet of height, so two miles of sewer.
Lestation, generator set, 20, 7 feet in the ground, some places, so we're in the rock.
That's a rare report.
A lot of stuff in it, so that's part of the price tag.
But when we started this project three years ago,
we were kind of in the three million range and then pipes on that.
And last year, with Resonance, we built pretty good with the number.
You know, much about the circle beam.
They had some pretty good reference stuff in their packet.
It does work in the unit.
They've done a ton of gas work.
They own six-year-olds, so they own all of their equipment.
So I think the only steps they had is like fingers.
So I was kind of excited to see that.
So you said that pretty good references to the contact of references.
We had it, so like I said, we opened bits Thursday afternoon.
And we got everything turned in for the packet Thursday evening.
So we had to get Council today, since we're running up.
We're running out of council meetings.
Is there a couple of...
Did you call it competitive competitors?
And they said, yeah, they've been around for a long time.
I mean, they kind of...
This is what they do.
They do a lot of silver work because of what they specialize in.
We didn't have a couple of draw.
Because circle beam was dating.
They've been around forever.
So that's very numbers.
So the concerns I have that hopefully don't have this job that we had with one.
We've got currently going...
Are they going to do proper blocking of streets?
This one's out, you know, I feel...
This one's out, you know, I feel this one.
This one's out.
I don't have an inspector because it is federal money.
I don't have an inspector outside.
No offense off the holes that they leave.
Okay.
This is the part of...
We had to open up our resources in order to learn.
We got for $4.00 and this is taking money out of that.
This is one of the projects we had to set aside for it.
It's worth voting on is to approve this to go before a community to be approved.
Yes, so once we approve it then, we'll send it to open our resources.
Indeed.
So they can see that we've approved it.
So that I can approve all the paperwork on there.
And we're trying to get everything approved because...
You know, this contractor wants to let his vendors know that.
I've been awarded this bid so they can get their stuff locked in
because prices are fluctuating.
So when is it projected to start date on this?
He was thinking that we were in March.
When are they to start date on materials?
What is the projected timeline?
We haven't talked about, I mean...
You know, as far as the link at the time I came around.
The contract days are two hundred and seven.
This is being built to actually be everything more as a trash.
You have any concerns with them and try to start being quarter of a million dollars
as far as they miss something.
We actually have all of them as a team.
As a member, they were good with their number and they were still fine with it.
I mean, he, he, he, Joe, he used to, I wish I was a little bit closer.
You know, you're in the business too.
You don't want to, I believe that much money on the table.
A lot of money he left there.
Yeah.
But, you know.
What is the funding for this project come from?
Is it federal funded?
Yeah.
It's the ultimate water resources board.
So they have a, they have a drinking water division in a clean order.
This is kind of the clean water division in the funding.
So when do we start paying the spec?
We pay a back of the money spent.
So it has the money for a year, a year, a year.
Yeah.
And we don't pay interest on it until we start spending it.
And they've been very good about.
They got some extra money from the feds.
And so they wait to live on their thousand off the principle.
So there any time they get three money that they can help us out.
So.
So the questions I have.
So how do you feel about your answers?
Do you want your water?
Yeah.
I talked Tyler earlier today too.
Thank you.
I'll show you the crew.
I'll second.
Sunberg.
Hi.
Parker.
Davis.
Hi.
Nice to meet you all.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
10 staff reports.
11.
So moved.
Second.
He stepped on.
So cool.
Sunberg.